The eye is an exteriorized brain.
目は外在化した脳である。
The eye is an expansion of
目は、
your third ventricle.
あなたの第三脳室の拡張である。
It is ultimately connected to a small gland we call
それは最終的に、
the pineal gland.
松果体と呼ばれる小さな腺と関連している。
We think it's the pituitary gland, but ultimately it's the one that regulates one
脳下垂体だと思われがちだが、最終的にそれが、
of the richest energy qualities.
最も豊かなエネルギーの質の一つを調整している。
of your life, it's your sleep; not only must you
あなたの人生において、それはあなたの睡眠である。呼吸をしっかりするだけでなく、
breathe well, you must eat well,
しっかり呼吸し、しっかり食べる必要がある。
but above all, you must sleep well, and often we don't sleep well because we think
しかし何よりも、しっかり眠る必要がある。そして、考えすぎているために、しばしばよく眠れない。
too much,
考えすぎているからだ。
be fully aware of your inhalation, exercise, stand up,
自分の吸気に完全に意識を向けなさい。エクササイズ：立ち上がってください。
place your feet on the ground, but with your legs parallel,
足を地面につけ、脚は平行に。
Here, with parallel feet, you flex
ここで、足を平行にして、あなたは、
your knees just a little to open up here.
膝をほんの少し曲げて、ここを少し開くために。
Perform a slight pelvic retroversion to bring the
骨盤をわずかに後傾させ、
navel, the pubis, towards the xiphoid
臍、恥骨を剣状突起の方向へ導く。
process, very slight, you open slightly here and you
非常に軽く、ここでわずかに開き、あなたは〜を探す。
seek your anterior white line
あなたの前白線を探し、
your posterior white line and you seek the balance between the
あなたの後白線を探し、そしてその間のバランスを。
two.
二つの間で。
You close your eyes, you make contact with the ground, you
目を閉じ、地面と接触し、あなたは、
feel gravity, you feel the weight
重力を感じ、体の重さを感じる。
of your body on your feet.
足にかかるあなたの体の重さを。
You become aware of your urogenital system
あなたの泌尿生殖器系を意識しなさい。
which is a continuity.
それは連続体である。
Down to the level of your feet, you feel the ground, your heels, then
足のレベルまで、地面、かかとを感じ、そしてあなたは、
you connect with your vegetative, digestive system, the
あなたの植物性、消化器系、
abdomen, the vegetative world,
腹部、植物の世界に入りなさい。
ventre,  le  monde  végétal,
ventre,  le  monde  végétal,
the water.
水。
You relax; each level has a point of stillness; you
リラックスしてください、各レベルには静止点があります、あなたは
seek the stillness.
静寂を探します。
the stillness of the tissue. When you are well within your mineral kingdom, you
組織の静寂。あなたが鉱物界にしっかりといるとき、あなたは
can be well within
しっかりといることができます
your vegetal kingdom. These are the emotions, the
あなたの植物界に。それは感情です、その
basic emotions. This is the water. When you
基本的な感情。それは水です。あなたが
are
いるとき、
well relaxed, immobile, when you dare to be in immobility,
十分に緩んで、静止して、あなたが静止の中にいることを敢えてするとき、
you breathe down into your feet. Then
足の先まで呼吸します。それから
you enter your animal kingdom.
あなたは動物界に入ります。
The rhythms, this is the rhythmic zone.
リズム、それはリズムゾーンです。
The heart, the lungs, deglutition.
心臓、肺、嚥下。
You relax.
緩めてください。
You seek the point of stillness.
静止点を探します。
You seek the fulcrum.
支点を探します。
It is a posterior mesogastrium.
それは後方腸間膜です。
then you connect to the point between the eyes, you
それから、眉間の点に接続します、あなたは
relax, you seek immobility, you
緩めて、静止を探します、あなたは
concentrate
集中します
at the level of the eyes and at the level of the heels. When
目のレベルとかかとのレベルで。師に
one asks the master how long you must
どれくらいの時間あなたが
remain, he will answer you
留まるべきか尋ねると、彼は答えるでしょう
as much time
できるだけ長く
as you can remain.
あなたが留まることができる限り。
You release.
緩めてください。
Move your hands a little.
少し手を動かしてください。
Bring back some energy.
少しエネルギーを取り戻してください。
Like so.
このように。
We move everything a little.
全体を少し動かします。
To ensure proper circulation.
円滑な循環を促すため。